Tom Shaffir

Angular developer

tom.shaffir@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tom-shaffir-a36289125

https://tomshaffir.github.io/tom-portfolio



053-3320-792



Tel-Auiu



24/10/1987

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

A software development and performance engineering with 3 years of experience in the high-tech manufacturing and Internet industries. Strong analytical abilities, questioning mind and critical thinking, fast learner - quickly fits in, team player with great interpersonal skills, **changing position** towards FRONT-END developing, in particular ANGULAR 2+

EDUCATION

2017- 2018 Certificate: Angular 2+, JavaScript from Coursera and more (140+ Hours)

2012 - 2016 B.sc. in COMPUTER SCIENCE; Tel Hai College (GPA score: 85), Psychometric score: 720

2003 - 2006 Full matriculation; Math, Physics, English (5 Units), Emek High School (score: 106)

FRONT END PROFESSIONAL COURSES

Deeply learning & Hands-on Projects building on the following topics:

Angular 2+, Css 3, Javascript, Es5/Es6, Redux (basic), TypeScript, Bootstrap, Html 5, Angular styling & animations, Advanced Rxjs library

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2015-2017 Mellanox technologies, Linux drivers developer

- R&D team, Researching & Developing complex data traffic abilities (Infiniband).
- Drivers coding (Infiniband) on both C & Assembly.
- Using Scrum work method as a Team standard.
- Verifies items created or defined by developing and conducting tests (Python mainely).
- Consistently met deadlines for key projects before tape-out.
- Coordinates with hardware design engineers to provide effective system solutions.
- Increased revenue by assuming more projects and diligently completing all required tasks.
- Experience in Linux embedded systems development, Linux OS internals, with real time schedulers, multi-threaded programming and inter-process communications in Linux OS environment.

2014-2015 Vision Systems, RT embedded (student job)

- A student job assigned to RT embedded team.
- Hard real time developing for a navigation device.

2013 Computer science preparatory, Tel-hai college, Teacher assistant

- Teaching introduction to computer science, 5 level mathematics and Assembly.
- · Frontal teaching both groups & individuals.

MILITARY SERVICE

2006-2011 RANK: Officer captain (3 stripes). Permanent service as intelligence officer in Unit 76

TECHNOLOGIES & CODING

C, Assembly, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Firebase, Git, TCP/IP, OSPF, STP, IGMP, VRRP and more

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Primary Language | English - High Level